The Word I'm about to say is not mine.
Whatever mountain, whatever situation -
I decree it, in the name of Jesus!
This Innocent Looking Man Controlled 999 DEMONS
Be it an evil spirit that is tormenting your life, out!
Be it a contrary spirit that is hiding somewhere, tormenting your life,
I decree, in the name of Jesus, I say, out, in the name of Jesus!
I say, out, in the name of Jesus!
I say, be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
As Prophet T.B. Joshua offers mass prayer, many who are demon possessed are arrested.
You can see a man, laying on the floor behind these two women,
who had also been arrested because of the evil spirits they possessed.
My name is Kelechi.
I possess evil spirits and I have 333 powers.
I control 999 demons.
All this started when I went to school.
I used to go out and preach the gospel, I ministered healing to people,
I proclaimed the good news of the Lord, I published tracks
and shared them to people in buses and hospitals.
People listened and converted.
Because I saw the many things the man of God did on Emmanuel TV,
I wanted to be like him and have that power to become like him.
I was in a place sitting down and meditating.
Three boys came and told me about a place where I could get that power to do more than him.
I agreed to that because all I needed was the power to do more than him.
I followed them with all pleasure; no hesitation.
When I got there, the tune of the music changed.
What I saw there was not what I had expected.
I had to admit that and accept it.
I was initiated.
A woman then appeared, an old woman, very haggard and entered into my body.
That was how I began my duty.
I was given a duty, a mission for execution of duties.
I started that work.
What he is saying is that he is possessed, he has demons inside him,
where he is looking for power.
How can one be looking for power when we are born with it?
The Bible says, "Behold, I have given you".
So, what we need now is necessary faith to release the power.
He says he is looking for power.
When you are looking for power, you see demon's power, not God's power.
We don't look for God's power, it is there, but the power can remain dormant
when there is no necessary faith to release it.
Tell your neighbour, “There is power in my mouth”.
The belief in my heart is released by faith out of my mouth.
So, since your deliverance, how has your life been?
I feel relieved, I feel fine.
TT ROBERT BEGIER 04/10/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 09/10/2018